

PROFILE

Shravan is working as a Business Technology Analyst in the Financial Services Industry. He is interested in entrepreneurship and has built several software MVPs in college. He is experienced in building FullStack AI web / software. Comfortable working in an Agile environment and a passion for learning new technologies.

CONTACT / PROFILE













TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, Flask, Angular, JQuery, Bootstrap, MySQL, Google Cloud Platform, AWS

SOFT SKILLS

Integrity
Inclusiveness
Collaborative

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Participating in hackathons and attending business seminars (StarUp, Surat Jugaad, etc).

Inter NIT (National level) Cricket team member for NIT Surat.

IGNIS tournament - 1st place

DSO (Mumbai District) Kho Kho tournament (2nd place)

SHRAVAN SHETTY

Analyst @ Deloitte, https://shravanshetty.in

WORK EXPERIENCE

Analyst - Deloitte, July 2021 - Present

- 1. Strategized and built an internal tool to distribute rewards to the employees for their successful referrals. Technologies used: Python (Flask, Pandas), JQuery, File Operations, Bootstrap.
- 2. Product Quality for Charles River owned by State Street. Industry: Investment Management

Freelancing - Broadview Innovation, May 2021 – June 2021

- 1. Implemented Server-Side Rendering & social media sharing feature for the Eventilo web application.
- 2. Bug fixing support provided for 6 major bugs in the web application. Technologies used: Angular, Typescript, NodeJS.

EDUCATION

NIT Surat, Sardar Vallabhbhai National Institute of Technology

Engineering, July 2017 – July 2021

Participated & organized hackathons and events as an ACM executive

PERSONAL PROJECTS

<u>Dotmole</u> (Python, Flask, SQLite, OpenCV)

Server software that lets user connect their CCTV / IP cameras and PC to the server running Dotmole software. Dotmole runs face tracking, performs face management and video surveillance.

- 1. Technologies: Javascript, JQuery, Flask backend, REST-APIs.
- 2. Industry: Software, Home appliances.

Brokerage Calculator

Angular web application that calculates the extra costs associated with the intraday trading; Best used for high frequency intraday traders.

- 1. Future plans: Add sections for derivatives and other funds.
- 2. Technologies: Angular.
- 3. Industry: Software, Finance (stock market)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Hackathon / Dotslash – Agora track (3rd place)

Built Dotmole – We used Agora to get livestreams from cameras outside of the network. And built a video shortening service using Motion detection.

CERTIFICATION

<u>Essential Cloud Infrastructure: Foundation</u> <u>Google Cloud Platform Fundamentals: Core Infrastructure</u>